well this interview that
bueno esta entrevista que le ha hecho
wefere did with silberg okay he charged my
wefere a silberg vale le cobraba a mis
friends to play
amigos por jugar
with me he charged my friends to play
conmigo le cobraba los amigos por jugar
with him okay Well to be honest
con él vale Bueno a mí sinceramente
you had like one I would have liked more
tuviste como una me hubiera gustado más
now I tell you fight on Twitter that there
ahora os digo pelea en Twitter de que
was that you charged 10% for a group of
había que cobrabas 10% por a un grupo de
people like for or rather I would have liked him to
gente como por o sea me hubiera gustado
do it with the
que lo hiciera con el
doll what I understood that in the end I do
muñeco lo que entendí que que al final
n't know anything ok there goes nothing dude It's that
no sé nada va ahí va nada güey Es
I have to see but to give
que yo tengo a ver pero para dar
context for the people who are
contexto para la gente que esté
listening I mean what I understood was that
escuchando o sea lo que entendí era que
here pregnant women according to you
aquí las mujeres embarazadas según tú
are always fine with you handsome
siempre estamos bien contigo guapetón
cacao 4atro Love cacao cuat Love caca 4
cacao 4atro Love cacao cuat Love caca 4
kiss ma'am a kiss Ma'am thank you very much
beso señora un beso Señora muchas
only 100 members left To
gracias solo faltan 100 miembros Para
get to 2000 again say stop eh Only
volver a llegar a 2000 dice cesa eh Solo
100 left there are 1300
faltan 100 hay aquí 1300
people here it would be nice it would be nice to
personas estaría bien estaría bien
arrive eh you had like a group of friends
llegar eh tenías como un grupo de amigos
yes and you charged them to be your friend I mean that's what I
sí y las cobrabas por ser tu amigo o sea
saw no no [ __ ] your
es lo que lo que vi no no Chingas a tu
mother  Dude I was in my [ __ ]
madre güey estaba en mi mero [__]
Prime dad we had [ __ ] 200k viewers
Prime papá teníamos [__] 200k viewers
we were doing great dude So I
andábamos a toda madre güey Entonces yo
have to create content dude What do I do to
ocupo crear contenido güey Qué hago para
create content
crear contenido 200.000 espectadores
Silver handled 200,000 viewers in its time Prime
manejaba Silver en su época Prime
handled 200,000 viewers well band not
200.000 espectadores manejaba pues banda
even jh dared to do that much but the
ni jh se atrevió a tanto total pero la
[ __ ] band see the person the person
[__] banda ver la persona la persona
more not willing to work the most is
más no dispuesta a trabajar las más es
another [ __ ] life see How much money does the
otra [__] vida ver Cuánta pasta tiene
live shows of 200,000
que generar los directos de 200.000
viewers have to generate man How much money can that
espectadores tío Cuánta pasta puede
generate has he gone crazy it
generar eso se le ha ido la olla no ha
wasn't an exaggeration No no it's literal no
sido una exageración No no es literal no
what he said you don't understand me you're
lo que ha dicho no me entiendes tú eres
a person here [ __ ] awesome podcast damn
una persona aquí [__] podcast chingón
you're not worth [ __ ] but you put on your
puñetas no vales [__] pero te pones el
helmet pa and you're the [ __ ]
casco pa y eres la meda
[ __ ] I don't know if that was a compliment or I didn't
riata no sé si eso fue un cumplido o no
understand but thanks I'm
entendí pero gracias Es que estoy
talking not as if it doesn't exist But anyway what I'm
hablando no as como que no existe Pero
saying you put on your helmet
bueno lo que digo tú te pones el casco
you're another [ __ ] person geey you're the
eres otro [__] persona geey eres el
best Even if your life has depression in
mejor Aunque tu vida tenga depresión en
it  life in real life here you
la vida en la vida real acá
are You have friends you have friends nobody
eres Tienes amigas tienes amigos nadie
treats you bad for who you are you can be a
te trata mal por como eres puedes una
fat person and end up being okay [ __ ]
persona gorda y acaer está bien [__]
skinny fed up with mom ent people
flaco mamado de la mam ent la gente se
get into that world a lot a lot I'm not
mete mucho en ese mundo pero mucho Yo no
gay I'm one of those I get involved I make my mess and
gey yo es de me meto hago mi desmadre y
I go out on my own so I struggle a
me salgo en mi jale
lot with these people
entonces Batallo mucho con esas personas
when I want to work I need a team
cuando quiero trabajar ocupo un equipo
to roleplay what roleplaying I imagine yes
para rolear que rolear me imagino que sí
not to do our sketches damn
no hacer nuestras sketches puñetas
[ __ ] that are laughable So these
[__] que queden risa Entonces esta
people well dude I said You know what I'm going to
gente pues güey dije Sabes que te voy a
bring you dude and we're going to create this
traer a ti güey y vamos a crear este
system where I'm going to give you the josa with
sistema donde te voy a dar el josa con
the 20k dude the H will come to you the
los 20k güey te va a llegar el H a ti el
next day and you the other and you the
día siguiente y a ti el otro y a ti el
other but well the only thing I ask of them
otro pero pues lo único que les pido
dude is the
güey es el el el
10% which is nothing and you're not going to earn
10% que no es nada gy no van a ganar ni
a single [ __ ] dollar the most they
un [__] dólar lo máximo que me
ever paid me was some [ __ ] who's
llegaron a pagar fue un cabrón que
doing well right now and is super
ahorita le está yendo bien y está super
grateful  they were like geey $
agradecido fueron como que geey $
also $ the guy took $ 1,000 us
también $ se el vato se llevó $1,000 nos
a mom like that then Ah I mean okay I mean
una mam así entonces Ah o sea vale o sea
he
él le
offered him of course let's see him playing with
ofrecía claro a ver él jugando con
others those others
otros esos otros
eh of course him playing with others those others
eh claro él jugando con otros esos otros
took grandpa he missed you You had us
se llevaban abuelo se te extrañaba Nos
abandoned it's that Ivan I can't it's that I
abandonados es que Iván no puedo es que
have you so spoiled eh I mean
os tengo mu mal acostumbrados eh o sea
I don't know if there are other youtubers
es que no sé yo si hay otros youtubers
who are here all day eh every
que estén todo el día aquí eh todos los
day Here I have you very bad very bad very
días Aquí os tengo muy mal muy mal muy
bad of course let's see I understand the plan is
mal claro a ver entiendo el plan es
[ __ ] you're winning everything for these at
[__] estáis ganando todo para estas a
my expense give me
Costa mía darme
something the guy appreciated it the guy right now he's
algo el vato apreció el vato ahorita le
giving it to him with mother because he knew how
está dendo con madre porque supo
to work the others nothing they acted like
chambiar los demás nada se hicieron
fools and then they were complaining and
[__] y luego se estaban quejando y
what are you taking 10% from me and I say
queé me estás quitando el 10% y digo
geey you win [ __ ] 10 gey give me a [ __ ]
geey ganas pinches 10 gey me aar un [__]
dollar or I don't know how much it is but I say don't
dólar o no sé cuánto es pero digo no
[ __ ] with me I mean lower it but they just wanted to
[__] o sea bájele pero n más querían
make salsa they wanted to talk they wanted to
hacer salsa querían platicar querían
make more filler Yo  I'm more important
hacer más relleno Yo soy más importante
and in the end he asked them for 10% of what they
y al final les pedía el 10% de lo que
earned thanks to the promo that they
ganaban gracias a la promo que ellos les
gave them okay not bad
daba está bien no está mal
alne not
alne no está nada
bad at all not bad at all that eh is a good
mal no está nada mal eso eh es buena
idea I'm going to apply it I'm going to apply it Well
idea lo voy a aplicar lo voy a aplica
if you're offering something that is
Pues si estás ofreciendo algo que es
Elo Prime exposure and whatever it is that they
exposición Elo Prime y cualquier es que
can collaborate with him and precisely
pueden colaborar con él y precisamente
thanks to that dedicating yourself to this that
gracias a eso dedicarse a esto que
dedicating yourself to this not
dedicarse a esto no lo consigue
everyone can get And there are people who don't who don't
cualquiera Y hay gente que no que no se
understand that it seems fair to me
entera de eso a mí me parece
then we have others like you who have it for
justo luego tenemos a otros como tú haen
free well
gratis bueno
eh Let's see it's that this guy also has his
eh A ver es que también este chico tiene
head all the time in the money
la cabeza todo el tiempo en en el dinero
and in the no I mean in the money in the
y en el no O sea en el dinero en el
business he always sees it he sees everything as a
negocio lo ve siempre lo ve todo como un
business here
negocio aquí
well Cos I was telling you Hey you know
bueno Cos te estaba diciendo Oye sabes
what I saw this video I'll play you know 10%
qué vi este video tocaré ya sabes 10%
papu with nimu is not cheaper no no no
papu con nimu no sale más barato no no
no 10% papu inco if you want to come back
no no el 10% papu inco si queréis volver
to the debates the 10% papu
a venir a los debates el 10% papu te
was cool but it's missing such such such no
quedó chido pero falta tal tal tal no
also like all the mess is behind the
también como todo el desmadre sea detrás
final fund  is and something and you're
fondo final es and algo y lo estás
charging for it, I mean, no way. Well, it's a
cobrando o sea ni pedo No pues es un
business at the end of the day, I mean,
negocio a final de cuentas o sea como
like what you were saying, no, people
que como lo que decías no que la gente
forget that this is a race and
se le olvida que esto es una carrera y
that it's a business at the end of the day. Yes, I
que es un negocio al final de cuentas Sí
mean, that's what I, that's why I wanted you to
o sea es que es lo que yo por eso quería
explain it a little more because in
que lo explicaras un poco más porque de
fact I even told Tony that it
hecho hasta le platiqué a a Tony el que
's the day, it's not that we were
que es el día no es que estábamos
talking and they asked me that question Like that I
hablando y me pusieron esa pregunta Como
charge 10% and I even told them, I
de que cobre el 10% y hasta les dije o
mean, literally on WhatsApp I put my
sea literal en WhatsApp le puse mi
team Hey, but what's the problem, I mean, I did
equipo Oigan Pero cuál es el pedo o sea
n't understand What's the controversy, literally,
no entendí Cuál es la polémica literal
because it's normal, right? I mean, well, you
porque pues es lo normal no O sea pues
're giving, I mean, it's an exchange if you do
estás dando o sea es un intercambio si
n't want to give it, then no, and they don't give you the
no quieres darlo pues no y no te dan el
Host and the reason why it's even
Host y ya la razón por qu hasta es el
10% geey, I mean, it was to set up a
10% geey o sea era para poner un
contract and so that the guys were like
contrato y que los vatos estuvieran como
formalized to the work more than anything, I
formalizados al trabajo más que todo o
mean, to collaborate, to collaborate with him
sea que colaboren que colaboren con él
regularly, I mean, but trust you, Auron,
habitualmente o sea pero fíate tú auron
for example, too. I should have
por ejemplo también Tendría que haber
done that, damn it  Wow, Auron hasn't given
hecho eso [__] anda que no le ha dado
people work. Eh, I mean
trabajo auron a la gente Eh o sea
literally, okay, you're always
literalmente vale ustedes siempre estáis
here with me in my games, you play
aquí conmigo en mis partidas jugáis
with me and such. You're going to, You're going to, You
conmigo y tal Vais a Vais a Vais a tener
're going to have H, You're going to have spectators, but of
H Vais a tener espectadores pero de
your monthly salary, 10% is for me,
vuestro sueldo al mes un 10% es para mí
signed, not bad, eh, I mean, not bad,
firmado no está mal eh o sea no está mal
eh, I'm going to do it from now on
eh lo voy a hacer yo a partir de ahora
with Isco and with him, I'll
con isco y con el
play in the rest of the businesses. People
tocaré en el resto de negocios la gente
don't throw their hands up in the air. I'll
no se echa las manos en la cabeza yo te
promote your business in exchange for 10%.
promociono tu negocio a cambio de un 10%
Where's the bad thing? No, no, no, no, no, it's not bad, it's not bad, it's not bad, it's not bad, it's okay, it's
Dónde está lo malo no no no no no no es
okay.
es malo está bien está bien